[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first mate of the fictional USS Stingray, commanded by Lieutenant Commander Thomas Dodge?", "correct_answer": "Martin T. Pascal", "incorrect_answers": ["E.T. Lovacelli", "Yancy Graham", "Jefferson Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This syndrome or disorder occurs after a very traumatic event and has intense symptoms such as reliving the event over and over.", "correct_answer": "Post Traumatic Stress Disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Seasonal Affect Syndrome", "Bi-Polar Disorder", "Attention Deficit Disorder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the real name of the Penguin, one of Batmans greatest enemies?", "correct_answer": "Oswald Cobblepot", "incorrect_answers": ["Max Shreck", "james gordon", "danny devito"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This English rock musician changed his name to avoid confusion with a singer from the Monkees, who had the same family name.", "correct_answer": "David Bowie", "incorrect_answers": ["Elvis Costello", "David Crosby", "Earl The Monkey  Hinson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was Nicolas Appert vital in the success of Napoleon?", "correct_answer": "He was one of Napoleons cooks", "incorrect_answers": ["He became Field Marshall Ney, head of the Cavalry", "He was Napoleons top spy", "He was responsible for Napoleons favorite horse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first song that radio personality and voice actor Casey Kasem played on his radio show Americas Top Forty?", "correct_answer": "Mama Told Me Not to Come", "incorrect_answers": ["Forget Him", "Mandy", "Love Me Tender"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the tagline of the 2000 horror movie parody Scary Movie?", "correct_answer": "No mercy. No shame. No sequel.", "incorrect_answers": ["Do you see dead people?", "The youngest and most beautiful corpses youll ever see!", "Get ready to pee in your pants!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actor in 1994?", "correct_answer": "Burt Reynolds in Cop and a Half", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Redford in Indecent Proposal", "Arnold Schwarzenegger in Last Action Hero", "Willem Dafoe in Body of Evidence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these celebrities was named after the Biblical character who was Namomis daughter-in-law?", "correct_answer": "Oprah Winfrey", "incorrect_answers": ["Moonunit Zappa", "Uma Thurman", "Penelope Cruz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Freddy Krueger made a deal with the Dream Demon and ended his mortal life. What was his mortal body buried in?", "correct_answer": "The trunk of a car", "incorrect_answers": ["A locked safe", "The bottom of the ocean", "A very ancient Oriental Cabinet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Lean on Me Joe Clark is caught with chains on the doors by the mayor of Paterson, NJ.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is covered by the 19th amendment to the US constitution?", "correct_answer": "Voting rights for women", "incorrect_answers": ["Voting rights for citizens of Washington, D.C.", "Repeal of Prohibition", "Voting rights for people of Guam"]}]